ejuice.deals 2019-12-04

# Privacy Policy — eJuice.Deals

Privacy Policy 

We at ejuice.deals at take your privacy very seriously. Read the information below to learn more about our privacy policy. 

What This Policy Covers   
This privacy policy covers how Ejuice.Deals Inc (“we”) treats the information that we collect regarding visitors and users (“you”) of the Ejuice.Deals.com site.

The Information That We Collect About You   
We collect certain information that you voluntarily give to us when you use the Ejuice.Deals.com site, such as when you establish an account, place an order, or contact us. This information may include your first and last name, mailing address, email address, shipping address, telephone number, date of birth, credit card information, username and password, and any other information that is necessary for us to provide our products and services. We may also require you to provide a driver’s license or government issued identification to verify your age and eligibility to purchase tobacco products from us. You may choose not to provide any information. However, a decision not to provide the information we request may mean that you cannot obtain a product or service from us or use certain features of the site.

You may provide us with information about other individuals (for example, you may request shipping to another individual and their address). We will use and handle such information in accordance with this privacy policy.

We also collect certain technical information about you automatically when you visit the Ejuice.Deals.com site. Such information may include your IP (Internet Protocol) address, mobile device identifier, browser type and operating system, the identity of the web site you visited prior to visiting Ejuice.Deals.com, clickstream data (e.g., pages viewed and time spent), and access times. We use this information, which does not allow us to contact you personally, to understand and analyze trends, administer the site, learn about user behavior at the site, and gather demographic information about our users as a whole. 

How We Use and Share Your Information   
Information collected about you is collected for the purpose of serving you, administering the site, and providing and improving our products and services. We use your information to process your orders, communicate with you about an order you have placed, ship products that you order, respond to questions you may pose to us, resolve problems and disputes, and communicate with you about products or services that we believe may interest you. We may use this information to communicate with you under a number of circumstances, such as in response to a request from you for information, notification of changes in our policies, distribution of our monthly newsletter, or contact regarding your account with us. As we serve you, it becomes necessary to share your personal information with other entities who need the information to provide services for us. (For example, may share your information with service providers and agents to fulfill your requests and orders, process payments, perform analytics, provide you with information and updates, and maintain, improve, and deliver the Ejuice.Deals.com site.) 

Use Of Your Information For Marketing Purposes   
When you provide personal information to us, you are automatically subscribed to our email newsletter and may receive other offers or marketing materials from us by email. You may opt out of these email contacts if you desire. Note, however, that you cannot opt-out of certain non-commercial, transactional e-mails that we may send from time to time. 

Use Of Cookies   
To enhance the benefit of Ejuice.Deals.com to you, we use “cookies.” Cookies are small text files we place on your computer. These files contain a small amount of data which can anonymously identify you to the Ejuice.Deals.com system. (For example, cookies help us keep track of a series of merchandise selections. The cookie tells us that the selections were made by the same visitor, but cookies by themselves do not tell us who the visitor is.) Cookies are used to track usage of the Ejuice.Deals.com site. Information we collect through cookies helps us to determine which pages are most popular with our users. You may be able to set your web browser to reject cookies. However, rejection of cookies may negatively affect your ability to use the Ejuice.Deals.com site. 

How You May Correct Information   
You may update or correct your personal information, by logging in to your account on Ejuice.Deals.com or by contacting us by e-mail at sales@Ejuice.Deals.com. 

Minor Children   
Ejuice.Deals.com is intended to be safely viewed by general audiences over the age of 18. No offensive material of any kind is welcome on Ejuice.Deals.com. We do not knowingly solicit orders from any individuals below the legal age to enter into a binding contract in their home jurisdiction.

What This Policy Does Not Cover   
We cannot state or control the policy of companies that we do not own or control, or people that we do not employ or manage. 

Protection of Your Information   
Although we strive to take appropriate measures to safeguard your personal information against unauthorized access, use or disclosure, Ejuice.Deals.com cannot guarantee absolute security, as no data transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. You transmit any information to us at your own risk, and you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and login information.

How To Contact Us   
If you have any questions, comments, suggestions, or wish to contact us for any reason, you may do so at: sales@Ejuice.Deals.com or sales@Ejuice.Deals.com. 

Updates  
We may update this privacy policy at any time, and we will notify you of any changes by, at a minimum, posting the updated privacy policy. We encourage you to review this policy each time you visit the Ejuice.Deals.com site so that your understanding of our policy will remain current.

Current as of: July 31, 2019
